[
    {
        "question": "Independent review and examination of records and activities to assess the adequacy of system controls, to ensure compliance with established policies and operational procedures. NIST SP 1800-15B",
        "answer": "Audit"
    },
    {
        "question": "An architectural approach to the design of buildings and spaces which emphasizes passive features to reduce the likelihood of criminal activity.",
        "answer": "Crime Prevention through Environmental Design (CPTED)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Information security strategy integrating people, technology, and operations capabilities to establish variable barriers across multiple layers and missions of the organization. Source: NIST SP 800-53 Rev 4",
        "answer": "Defense in Depth"
    },
    {
        "question": "A certain amount of access control is left to the discretion of the object's owner, or anyone else who is authorized to control the object's access. The owner can determine who should have access rights to an object and what those rights should be. NIST SP 800-192",
        "answer": "Discretionary Access Control (DAC)"
    },
    {
        "question": "To protect private information by putting it into a form that can only be read by people who have permission to do so.",
        "answer": "Encrypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Devices that enforce administrative security policies by filtering incoming traffic based on a set of rules.",
        "answer": "Firewalls"
    },
    {
        "question": "An entity with authorized access that has the potential to harm an information system through destruction, disclosure, modification of data, and/or denial of service.",
        "answer": "Insider Threat"
    },
    {
        "question": "An operating system manufactured by Apple Inc. Used for mobile devices.",
        "answer": "iOS"
    },
    {
        "question": "The use of multiple controls arranged in series to provide several consecutive controls to protect an asset; also called defense in depth.",
        "answer": "Layered Defense"
    },
    {
        "question": "An operating system that is open source, making its source code legally available to end users.",
        "answer": "Linux"
    },
    {
        "question": "A system irregularity that is identified when studying log entries which could represent events of interest for further surveillance.",
        "answer": "Log Anomaly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Collecting and storing user activities in a log, which is a record of the events occurring within an organization's systems and networks. NIST SP 1800-25B.",
        "answer": "logging"
    },
    {
        "question": "An automated system that controls an individual's ability to access one or more computer system resources, such as a workstation, network, application or database. A logical access control system requires the validation of an individual's identity through some mechanism, such as a PIN, card, biometric or other token. It has the capability to assign different access privileges to different individuals depending on their roles and responsibilities in an organization.",
        "answer": "Logical Access Control Systems"
    },
    {
        "question": "Access control that requires the system itself to manage access controls in accordance with the organization's security policies.",
        "answer": "Mandatory Access Control"
    },
    {
        "question": "An entrance to a building or an area that requires people to pass through two doors with only one door opened at a time.",
        "answer": "Mantrap"
    },
    {
        "question": "Passive information system-related entity (e.g., devices, files, records, tables, processes, programs, domains) containing or receiving information. Access to an object (by a subject) implies access to the information it contains.",
        "answer": "Object"
    },
    {
        "question": "Controls implemented through a tangible mechanism. Examples include walls, fences, guards, locks, etc. In modern organizations, many physical control systems are linked to technical/logical systems, such as badge readers connected to door locks.",
        "answer": "Physical Access Controls"
    },
    {
        "question": "The principle that users and programs should have only the minimum privileges necessary to complete their tasks.",
        "answer": "Principle of Least Privilege"
    },
    {
        "question": "An information system account with approved authorizations of a privileged user.",
        "answer": "Privileged Account"
    },
    {
        "question": "A type of malicious software that locks the computer screen or files, thus preventing or limiting a user from accessing their system and data until money is paid.",
        "answer": "Ransomware"
    },
    {
        "question": "An access control system that sets up user permissions based on roles.",
        "answer": "Role-based access control (RBAC)"
    },
    {
        "question": "An instruction developed to allow or deny access to a system by comparing the validated identity of the subject to an access control list.",
        "answer": "Rule"
    },
    {
        "question": "The practice of ensuring that an organizational process cannot be completed by a single person; forces collusion as a means to reduce insider threats. Also commonly known as Separation of Duties.",
        "answer": "Segregation of Duties"
    },
    {
        "question": "Generally an individual, process or device causing information to flow among objects or change to the system state.",
        "answer": "Subject"
    },
    {
        "question": "The security controls (i.e., safeguards or countermeasures) for an information system that are primarily implemented and executed by the information system through mechanisms contained in the hardware, software or firmware components of the system.",
        "answer": "Technical Controls"
    },
    {
        "question": "A one-way spinning door or barrier that allows only one person at a time to enter a building or pass through an area.",
        "answer": "Turnstile"
    },
    {
        "question": "An operating system used in software development.",
        "answer": "Unix"
    },
    {
        "question": "The process of creating, maintaining and deactivating user identities on a system.",
        "answer": "User Provisioning"
    }
]